IFSCL 9周年预告
翻译，时间轴，压制：Bolshevik0
I know who you are.
我知道你是谁
注：箱子上的字是「警告 有放射性」
我从未见过你这样的女孩儿
I've never known a girl like you before
就像置身于往日的歌谣
Now just like in a song from days of yore
你走过来敲着我的门
Here you come a knockin', knockin' on my door
我从未见过你这样的女孩儿
And I've never met a girl like you before
超级计算机
(Aelita的妈妈)
秘密
神经元耳机
量子场
迦太基
回到过去
老屋
虚拟化
边境(S1E19)
扫描器
回到过去
特工
美国
牺牲
多代理
红色天空
未来
死亡
流连于你的风格
You give me just a taste so I want more
而我现在遍体凌伤
Now my hands are bleeding and my knees are raw
你让我发现了我内心中的恶魔
You've made me acknowledge the devil in me
但愿我没有得罪你
I hope to God I'm talkin' metaphorically
但愿我讲得很委婉
Hope that I'm talkin' allegorically
即使我只是在表达我内心的真实感受
Know that I'm talkin' about the way I feel
也是因为我从未见过你这样的女孩儿
And I've never known a girl like you before
从 来 也 没 有
Never, never, never, never
感谢大家不停的支持
我从未见过你这样的女孩儿
Never known a girl like you before